<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Community Questions</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Community Questions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 17:05:17 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Immutability in Private Channels</title>
      <link>/posts/data-immutability-in-private-channels/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 17:05:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/data-immutability-in-private-channels/</guid>
      <description>Q: &amp;ldquo;How is data immutability in private channels implemented in Fabric? How can one establish which ledger stores valid history of transactions, if one party has forged data on its peer???&amp;rdquo;
Before beginning here is some fabric terminology I’ll be using in the post (all referenced from Here.)
Channel - A Hyperledger Fabric channel is a private “subnet” of communication between two or more specific network members, for conducting private and confidential transactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>/posts/difference-between-anchor-and-leader-peer-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 14:06:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/difference-between-anchor-and-leader-peer-/</guid>
      <description>Q: &amp;ldquo;Difference between anchor peer and leader peer in fabric??&amp;rdquo;
Every organization in Hyperledger fabric architecture can have multiple peers. When setting up a new channel, the participating organization and its associated peers, anchor peers and some other information are configured. This is done via a channel configuration transaction.
A channel configuration transaction holds the following information
 Participants in the channel – set of organizations
 Peers belonging to each participant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Number of Nodes</title>
      <link>/posts/number-of-nodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 11:29:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/number-of-nodes/</guid>
      <description>Q: &amp;ldquo;Unlike Ethereum or Bitcoin, they have many nodes, so the network is safe. but Hyperledger are permissioned distributed ledgers, does that mean less nodes in this network and less security?&amp;rdquo;
A: Number of nodes does not impact security in Hyperledger Fabric.
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the question. Based on the context where the question was found, Hyperledger here means Hyperledger Fabric.
I&amp;rsquo;ll assume basic knowledge of Bitcoin/Ethereum and continue from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Blockchain Fork Happen in Fabric?</title>
      <link>/posts/does-blockchain-fork-happen-in-fabric/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 10:33:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/does-blockchain-fork-happen-in-fabric/</guid>
      <description>Q: &amp;ldquo;does blockchain fork happen in fabric??&amp;rdquo;
A: No.
First of all, let&amp;rsquo;s start with the question. Blockchain fork is not one of the most cleanly defined terms out there, but let us go with the meaning of forks in Bitcoin blockchain. Fabrc on it&amp;rsquo;s own is supposed to mean &amp;ldquo;Hyperledger Fabric&amp;rdquo; which is the official term for the project. Link to the project site.
At this point, I am going to assume passing familiarity of Hyperledger Fabric and Bitcoin and continue from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is This?</title>
      <link>/posts/what-is-this/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 12:27:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/what-is-this/</guid>
      <description>What is this? This is an experimental approach to blogging. Rather than us choosing topics; we search around for questions out in the wild, (say Stack Overflow or other chat sites) which are surprisingly difficult to answer in a QA format and try to answer them in as detailed as we can.
We hope to write up technical responses that may be more detailed than the original question hoped or cared for, but perhaps may entertain other curious passer-bys on the wider internet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>